http://www.lakeflow.com/privacy/

LakeFlow.com
sales@dotevoke.com
Privacy policy
This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from Dot Evoke (the “Site”).INFORMATION WE COLLECT AS YOU USE OUR SERVICESWhen you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information” and it includes the following information:The web browser you used to access the Site.Your IP address.Your time zone.Some of the cookies that are installed on your device.Individual web pages or products that you view.Websites or search terms that referred you to the Site.Information about how you interact with the Site.We collect Device Information using the following technologies:Cookies: These are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. Visit All About Cookies for more information about cookies, including how to disable them.Server logs: These track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.Pixel tags: These are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
Additionally, when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you. We refer to this information as “Order Information” and it includes the following information:Your name.Your email address.Your IP address.Your phone number.
When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about both Device Information and Order Information.
HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
We use the Order Information that we collect so that we can respond to your inquiry or offer with a quote. Additionally, we use this information to communicate with you about our products or services. We only do this according to the preferences you have shared with us.
We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud. For example, your IP address is particularly useful for these purposes. We also use this information to improve and optimize the Site. For example, we generate analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns.
SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
We only share your Personal Information with a limited range of third parties in the limited range of scenarios described above. For example, in order to facilitate domain name transactions we use Escrow.com an escrow service. Occasionally for smaller transactions we may also utilize PayPal.
To help understand how our customers use the Site we use Google Analytics. You can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information and if you wish you can also opt-out of Google Analytics.
Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
DO NOT TRACK
Please note that we do not alter the Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.
YOUR RIGHTS
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, then please contact us.
Additionally, if you are a European resident, please note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (e.g. fulfill an order that you make through the Site) or to pursue any of the legitimate business interests described above. Also, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.
DATA RETENTION
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records. We retain these records indefinitely until you ask us to delete this information.
CHANGES
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
CONTACT US
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us.
